gemonline.tv 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy - GEM Online

### Our Refund Policy: 

We have a conditional refund policy which is based on customer dissatisfaction of our service. As long as the customer can provide us supporting documents regarding their issue with our system and the documents are matched with our monitoring systems we refund the whole payment immediately. 

### Our Privacy Policy: 

**Payment Information:**   
We do not have any access to your credit card information and we treat it as your fully confidential asset.   
**Personal/Activity Information:**   
We collect Information from you when you register on our site, fill out our forms, participate in our survays. Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * \- To personalize your experience( your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * \- To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * \- To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)   
To process transactions: Your Information, whether public or private, will not be sold ,exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent.
  * \- To send periodic emails The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order,in addition to receiving occasional company news,updates,related service information,etc.
  * \- We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.
  * \- We do not sell,trade,or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.
